<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<data-set xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<record>
		<title>Application selection administration settings</title>
		<description>Office 365 ProPlus provides thousands of configuration options via Group Policy and the Office Deployment Tool for Click-to-Run. Now administrators  can choose to exclude applications from the Office 365 ProPlus suite, such as Access or InfoPath. Updates to the Office Deployment Tool for Click-to-Run will enable administrators performing push deployments of Office 365 ProPlus to exclude one or more applications during the initial Office installation, or add/remove applications to an existing installation.</description>
		<category>launched</category>
		<linkID>XT104358093</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358144</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>DirSync tool with password hash sync as backup for Federated Sign-in</title>
		<description>Office 365 customers who use federated sign-in can now use DirSync with password hash sync as a backup in case there is a failure with any part of the on-premises identity provider. In case of failure you can reconfigure the Azure AD tenant from federated to standard in a matter of hours to enable sign-in.</description>
		<category>launched</category>
		<linkID>XT104358103</linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>End User Access to Quarantine for Exchange Online Protection</title>
		<description>End users can access their quarantined messages directly and release messages to their inbox. Previously, only admins had this capability.</description>
		<category>launched</category>
		<linkID>XT104358087</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358202</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Generic Top Level Domains administration settings</title>
		<description>Generic Top Level Domains (gTLD) can now be added directly from your Office 365 Admin Center.  Over 1,300 new gTLDs are now supported.</description>
		<category>launched</category>
		<linkID>XT104358082</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358132</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Lync for Mac update</title>
		<description>Lync for Mac now supports Enhanced 911 (E911) functionality with location awareness.  Additional improvements for the user experience included dynamic selection of a video camera while in a meeting and better file/picture transfer in IM and desktop sharing.</description>
		<category>launched</category>
		<linkID>XT104358096</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358109</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Match Subdomains in Exchange Online Protection</title>
		<description>The match subdomains feature enables you to send and receive emails on subdomains of a provisioned domain (aka Accepted Domain) in Office 365.</description>
		<category>launched</category>
		<linkID>XT104358087</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358110</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>OneNote for iOS 2.2.1 - iPhone update</title>
		<description>Three updates:First, It makes OneNote for iPhone a standalone experience with the ability to create new notebooks and sections. This means that you can now create a notebook, share it with others, and get on the same page - all from the convenience of an iPhone. Second, It dramatically improves the look and feel of OneNote on iOS 7 making note taking and navigation of your notes much more fluid and efficient.Third, we've added Office Lens to OneNote for iPhone. Similar to Office Lens on OneNote for iPad, this popular feature turns your iPhone into a pocket scanner so you can use it to take pictures of things like receipts, or whiteboard notes. Then, with Office Lens you can trim, enhance and makes pictures more readable. Best thing is, images are automatically synced to OneNote, and if your picture includes printed text, OneNote can recognize the text with optical character recognition (OCR) so you can search for words in the image.</description>
		<category>launched</category>
		<linkID>XT104358090</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358112</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Power Map now available to Office 365 subscriptions that include Excel</title>
		<description>Power Map for Excel is now available for all Office 365 subscriptions that include Excel.</description>
		<category>launched</category>
		<linkID>XT104358394</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358116</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Power View forecasting capabilities in Power BI for Office 365</title>
		<description>In Power View, you can now apply predictive forecasting, and hindcasting, when visualizing and exploring your data. Forecasting in Power View utilizes built-in predictive forecasting models using exponential smoothing to automatically detect seasonality in the data to provide forecast results from a series of data. Explore forecast results by adjusting the desired confidence interval or by adjusting outlier data to see how they affect results. You can also hindcast to see how Power View would have predicted the present and recent past based on older data.</description>
		<category>launched</category>
		<linkID>XT104358081</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358117</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Sign-In page branding for Office 365</title>
		<description>The Office 365 sign-in page can be branded with the additional purchase of Microsoft Azure AD Premium subscription. This subscription includes Company Branding which can be used to customize the sign-in page for all applications including Office 365, and also the Azure Management portal and the Azure Access Panel page.</description>
		<category>launched</category>
		<linkID>XT104358098</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358123</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Site folders in OneDrive for Business and SharePoint Online document libraries</title>
		<description>Added a new Site Folders view that takes you directly to document libraries of sites you’re following.  Now you can get to sites you’re following fast, right from OneDrive for Business.</description>
		<category>launched</category>
		<linkID>XT104358092</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358125</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Yammer localization expands to 28 languages</title>
		<description>The Yammer web experience now supports a total of 28 languages. You can easily select your preferred primary language from the language picker under Company Resources in your home page, under Access Options in a group, or in the footer of every page that doesn’t ssupport infinite scrolling, default is “English (US)”.</description>
		<category>launched</category>
		<linkID>XT104358104</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358128</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Yammer mobile apps support 12 languages</title>
		<description>Yammer mobile apps now support 12 languages across iOS, Android and Windows Yammer Notifier.  We are also taking mobile localization a step further, with inline message translation: a translate button will appear below the initial post. Clicking translate will instantly convert the entire conversation, including related responses, into the user’s default language.</description>
		<category>launched</category>
		<linkID>XT104358104</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358129</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Customizable SharePoint Online navigation bar</title>
		<description>A new SharePoint Online admin center feature that allows admins the ability to show or hide "Newsfeed/Yammer," "Sites" and "OneDrive for Business" for their users' Office 365 navigation bar experience.</description>
		<category>rollingout</category>
		<linkID>XT104358101</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358122</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Document Conversations for OneDrive for Business and SharePoint Online</title>
		<description>Document conversations enable people to share ideas and expertise around Office documents, images and videos, directly in the context of editing or reviewing. When opening a file stored in SharePoint Online or OneDrive for Business in your browser, the file is opened on the left and a contextual Yammer conversation is shown on the right, side by side. You can collapse and expand the Yammer pane as needed. You can start Yammer conversations around content, @mention coworkers on files, and publish to Yammer groups—either public or private. You can also view and participate in conversations outside your document, on your mobile device, in Microsoft Dynamics CRM or any app where a Yammer feed is embedded.</description>
		<category>rollingout</category>
		<linkID>XT104358095</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358195</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>External Sharing administration settings</title>
		<description>External collaboration settings have been consolidated into one place in the Office 365 Admin Center for admins to enable the access of their SharePoint sites and Exchange calendars with external organizations. In addition, admins can also enable their users to communicate with people outside of their organization using Lync.</description>
		<category>rollingout</category>
		<linkID>XT104358094</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358209</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>First Release for Office 365</title>
		<description>Office 365 continuously delivers product innovations – like new email or collaboration capabilities – as they become available. To help you best manage how you embrace new feature updates to your Office 365 subscription, we give you the choice to either follow our Standard Release process or opted into the First Release program for a select set of significant updates to the service.  First Release includes a selection of enhancements to the Office 365 user experience for SharePoint Online and Exchange Online. Tenants that opt into First Release will receive new qualifying feature update a minimum of two weeks before customers on Standard Release.</description>
		<category>rollingout</category>
		<linkID>XT104358080</linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>MAPI over HTTP for Outlook 2013 and Exchange Online</title>
		<description>MAPI over HTTP is a new transport used to connect Outlook and Exchange. It is the long term replacement for RPC over HTTP connectivity (commonly referred to as Outlook Anywhere). MAPI/HTTP removes the complexity of Outlook Anywhere’s dependency on the legacy RPC technology.</description>
		<category>rollingout</category>
		<linkID>XT104358099</linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>OS and Browser User Reports for Office 365</title>
		<description>Know which devices and browsers your users are using.  The operating system and browser reports provide you with summary and user access views of the types of operating systems and browsers accessing your Office 365 environment.</description>
		<category>rollingout</category>
		<linkID>XT104358082</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358153</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>OWA for Android Phone</title>
		<description>A native mobile app on Android phones that offers the same email, calendar and contact functionality you get in Outlook Web App, but with additional capabilities that are only possible through native integration of the app with the device.</description>
		<category>rollingout</category>
		<linkID>XT104358097</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358115</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Proactive DNS Records Check administration settings</title>
		<description>Customer DNS records are now automatically checked for potential issues.  If potential issues are identified, admins are notified and actions are proposed.  Subscribers with GoDaddy hosted domains have the option to have Office 365 automatically update the DNS records.  For all other DNS hosts, admins will be provided with the correct DNS records and instructions on how to correct them.  A confirmation screen will notify the admins once all issues are corrected.If custom DNS records are used in the tenant, admins are provided with the option to turn off the DNS records check to eliminate the error notifications.</description>
		<category>rollingout</category>
		<linkID>XT104358094</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358118</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Simplified admin user interface for Office 365</title>
		<description>Improves usability to enable admins to complete common admin tasks quickly.  Simplifications include a new user creation workflow with a single form, automatic license assignment, and confirmation page.  The user profile detail panel contains more user information including assigned license and alias email addresses.  Admins can optionally manually assign set passwords for new users.</description>
		<category>rollingout</category>
		<linkID>XT104358094</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358124</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Smart Search for OneDrive for Business</title>
		<description>The new OneDrive for Business search box is now smarter, with type-ahead features helping you find a document that might have been shared with you, or one that you tucked away several folders deep. You can also perform actions, like sharing these files, directly from the search results. Finding files and sharing them is even faster with the improved search box.</description>
		<category>rollingout</category>
		<linkID>XT104358092</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358126</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Apps for Office for Excel Online</title>
		<description>Excel Online will support adding Apps for Office similar to the Excel desktop client.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID></linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Apps for Office formatting APIs for Excel Online</title>
		<description>This feature allows Apps for Office that are opened used in Excel Online APIs to take advantage of the Format.js APIs that are already present in the desktop client capabilities.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID></linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Azure Active Directory Sync Services</title>
		<description>Azure AD Sync Services is a new identity sync tool that provides customers with the ability to sync identity information from complex AD environments, including ones with multiple forests, and other identity directories as Generic LDAP v3, PowerShell, CSV, Generic SQL through ODBC driver and Generic Web Services. A Beta is available now. It will support AAD Premium features and be a step-up from DirSync for more advanced configurations.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID>XT104358076</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358148</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Card View in Outlook Web App</title>
		<description>Group conversations in the list view are organized in cards which are a more consumable format for group interactions especially on mobile devices.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID>XT104358077</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358158</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Clutter for Outlook Web App</title>
		<description>Clutter is a separate view in the inbox where lower priority email appear. These items are removed from the standard inbox view so that the user can focus on the higher priority messages in the inbox.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID>XT104358077</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358178</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Codename Oslo &amp; Office Graph</title>
		<description>Codename Oslo is the first app to use the power of the Office Graph. Codename Oslo is a new way to search and discover content across Office 365 based on personalized insights. Oslo will be available for Windows 8 app, mobile devices, and integrated in the Office 365 web experience.  Office Graph is an underling technology and a suite-wide intelligence fabric that will help you discover content and make new connections. The Office Graph represents a collection of analyzed signals via machine learning, also called insights. These new insights are derived from each user’s behavior, their relationships to content, topics and one another. Content and signals are captured from Exchange Online, SharePoint Online, and Yammer.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID>XT104358078</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358114</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>CSOM Batching for Apps for SharePoint</title>
		<description>This feature allows CSOM calls to the apps for SharePoint APIs to be batched and executed in bulk rather than individually.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID></linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Custom Themes</title>
		<description>All customers will now have the capability to create custom themes for their end users.  This includes a clickable custom logo and customizable colors for top navigation bar, menu icons and text and the Office 365 logo.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID></linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358173</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Data Loss Prevention (DLP) in SharePoint Online</title>
		<description>Data loss prevention for SharePoint Online will help to identify sensitive data stored in SharePoint content libraries. With this capability, you will be able to perform eDiscovery searches for sensitive content in these SharePoint libraries. Sensitive content detections will be stamped/available in the FAST index for query and integration with search and classification results can be easily exported.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID>XT104358079</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358183</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>DKIM Outbound for Exchange Online Protection</title>
		<description>Exchange Online Protection will begin supporting outbound validation of Domain Keys Identified Mail (DKIM; see DomainKeys Identified Mail Signatures). DKIM is a method of validating a digitally signed message that appears in the DKIM-Signature header in the message headers. It ties an email message to the organization responsible for the message.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID>XT104358083</linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Document Collaboration in Outlook Web App</title>
		<description>Enhanced document collaboration in Outlook Web App allows a user to open a document from email and edit the document side-by-side with the original conversation using the Office Web Apps. The user can then reply to the original conversation with an edited version of the document automatically attached to the response.  The document can either be physically attached to the original email or stored in OneDrive for Business.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID>XT104358077</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358188</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Email Reminders for Meetings in Outlook Web App</title>
		<description>The ability to set-up automatic email reminders for meetings and other calendar events in Outlook Web App.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID></linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Enhanced Mail Protection Reporting</title>
		<description>Mail protection reports will include a more interactive reporting experience for Exchange Online and Exchange Online Protection admins.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID></linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Exchange Online Public Folder scale increase</title>
		<description>The limit of Exchange Online Public Folder count will be increased from 10,000 folders to 100,000 total folders. 
Full hierarchy sync has been improved to the point where it can scale linearly as folder count grows within the environment. There have also been storage optimizations which will provide better performance when accessing public folders.
</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID>XT104358100</linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Groups for Office 365</title>
		<description>Groups is a cross-suite experience unifying People, Conversations, Calendars, and Files across O365, enabling seamless collaboration across applications. Creating a Group anywhere in Office 365 will automatically provision a Yammer conversation feed, inbox, calendar and document library where members can collaborate and work as a team. Just like in Yammer, Groups are open by default but can be made private if necessary, enhancing discoverability and sharing.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID>XT104358085</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358215</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Increasing OneDrive for Business Storage to 1TB</title>
		<description>OneDrive for Business users will see their storage increased from 25 GBs to 1 TB of storage space.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID>XT104358089</linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Increasing Recoverable Items Quota for Users on Hold in Exchange Online</title>
		<description>By default, the recoverable items quota is set to 30 GB for all users. We are now increasing the Recoverable Items Quota to 100 GB for all users placed on In-Place Hold or Litigation Hold.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID></linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Office 2013 client update to support passive authentication using SAML</title>
		<description>Office 2013 rich client applications currently use the MS Sign-in Assistant to log into Office 365. This only supports the WS-Trust protocol and is not usable with any identity providers that require passive authentication with web page redirects such as WS-Federation and SAML/P. This feature is to enable Office rich client applications to work with third party Identity Providers and to work with the Windows Azure Multi-Factor Authentication implementation.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID>XT104358086</linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Office 365 navigation bar updates</title>
		<description>A new persistent navigation bar across Office 365 services simplifies navigation and bringing system alerts, reminders and new mail notifications cross suite.  The updated navigation bar will dynamically scale to accommodate different display widths. If the display is wide enough, all menu items will be visible. If the display is narrow, the additional menu items will automatically be added to the more menu (ellipses).  “My profile” controls will now be accessed via your photo which can be easily edited from any Office 365 service.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID></linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Office 365 Video</title>
		<description>Office 365 Video is a secure, company-wide destination for video upload, sharing and discovery, and smooth playback across devices - all powered by Windows Azure Media Services.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID>XT104358393</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358111</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Office App Store recommendation algorithm improvements</title>
		<description>This update will improve the recommendations algorithm for the Office App Store to be more precise and more relevant in the apps recommendations that it presents to users.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID></linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Office App Store removing sign-in requirement for free and trial apps</title>
		<description>This update will remove the need for customers to sign-in when adding a free or trial app to their Office 365 experience.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID></linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Office Online in Yammer</title>
		<description>With Office Online support in Yammer, documents uploaded to Yammer can be viewed and edited with Office Online, directly in Yammer. This allows documents to be beautifully rendered with Office Online, enables co-authoring by different users simultaneously, and displays relevant Yammer conversations, right on your browser.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID></linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358395</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>OneNote for Mac support for OneDrive for Business</title>
		<description>This update will enable OneNote for Mac to open, create, and edit Notebooks stored in OneDrive for Business and SharePoint Online.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID>XT104358091</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358113</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Pre-configured Apps for Office Preview for Word Online</title>
		<description>This Preview feature will enabled some users to see pre-configured apps in the Word Online ribbon for better exposure and visibility of the apps in the Office interface.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID></linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Preserving DL Membership &amp; BCC for Exchange In-Place Hold</title>
		<description>This update that will make DL membership &amp; BCC searchable for users placed on In-place Hold.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID></linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358131</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Propose New Time in Outlook Web App</title>
		<description>Enables users to propose a new time in response to a calendar invite in Outlook Web App.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID></linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Search Refiners in Outlook Web App</title>
		<description>Search refiners in Outlook Web App allow users to filter their search results faster. When a user types a new search query, a menu appears below the search bar with a list of options to refine the search results by sender, date, folder, and attachments.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID></linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358119</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Search Suggestions in Outlook Web App</title>
		<description>Search suggestions in Outlook Web App are recommended search terms that appear when a user starts typing a new search query. The recommendations are based on the user's mailbox content including the history of search results and keywords commonly found in email messages.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID></linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Send As Link to OneDrive for Business</title>
		<description>Send as link to OneDrive for Business allows a user to email a link to a document in OneDrive for Business in place of a physical attachment in Outlook Web App. Similar to a physical attachment, the link appears in the attachment well as an icon with a cloud on the front.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID>XT104358077</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358120</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Shared Computer Activation for Office 365 ProPlus</title>
		<description>Shared Computer Activation can be enabled during the installation of Office 365 ProPlus using the Office Deployment Tool. Once enabled, Office installs without being activated. When a user signs in to a computer with Office installed via Share Computer Activation, Office will check to see if the user has been provisioned for Office 365 ProPlus and temporarily activate Office 365 ProPlus until that user logs out.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID>XT104358093</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358121</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>SharePoint Online encryption at rest</title>
		<description>SharePoint Online Encryption at rest will provide BitLocker encryption by default on all customer document libraries, users' OneDrive for Business and site data - when they reside in the Office 365 datacenters. SharePoint Online and OneDrive for Business have always provide encryption in-transit. Now your content is secure be it in motion or at rest.
</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID>XT104358079</linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Single Identity for Office 365 and Yammer</title>
		<description>Office 365 users will be able to seamlessly access Yammer from their Office 365 navigation bar, providing immediate access to their existing Yammer account. Users will be able to authentic through Office 365 and toggle to Yammer without additional authentication. Office 365 users without existing Yammer accounts will be taken through a simplified sign up and verification flow.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID>XT104358084</linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358130</imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>User &amp; Groups in Exchange Online Protection</title>
		<description>Exchange Online Protection standalone and Exchange Enterprise CAL with Services subscribers can now directly manage recipients from within the Exchange admin center (EAC). This includes the ability to add, edit, or delete mail-enabled users (mail recipients who are internal to the organization) from the EAC and the ability to use mail enabled users as part of filtering policies and rules.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID>XT104358087</linkID>
		<imageID></imageID>
	</record>
	<record>
		<title>Weather Bar in Outlook Web App</title>
		<description>The calendar in Outlook Web App indicates the current local weather.</description>
		<category>inprogress</category>
		<linkID></linkID>
		<imageID>ZA104358127</imageID>
	</record>
</data-set>